Go to sleep when it's my birthday.
You should like 8:02 PM.  There
are Mondays that you simply have to
celebrate as Fridays, because Friday
is still too far away and the week so far has been far too
bad.  And go to
sleep at 8:02 PM.  I was so
grateful it was only 2 minutes later than usual for
my day.  I basically had
appointments all day.  Somehow,
none of the appointments worked out the way I wanted.
Among other things, I had to wait an hour
at the doctor's office.  I was absolutely exhausted,
and I'm usually in
the shower at 4 pm for my
evening routine.
I really only
did the bare minimum in the shower.  I really didn't feel like watching another
Everything
show.  We
actually wanted to do everything the same way this Monday evening as on
Friday evening, but no, I did
n't feel like an everything shower today.
Among other things, I also had
my ankle tattoo lasered off that day;
it was excruciatingly painful.  Afterwards,
I always get a bit of a
headache.  They were definitely gone after
the shower
.  I think it was simply
the stress.  I
bought a squishy toy today to
relieve stress.  Okay,
because I simply wanted to celebrate Monday as Friday
, I had a really
big pizza.  I'm not in the mood for all that
healthy nonsense today.  I want
something awesome.  My boy kept saying,
"Yeah, don't put too many
pieces in the pasta sauce."  I have to
explain five times that I'm
not making pasta today.  He didn't get it,
actually I wanted to make pasta,
but I
changed my mind shortly before because it was Pizza Friday, even though it was
Monday,
but we still had something to celebrate,
so like on Fridays we had a glass of
wine, it was lovely.  Later
I brushed my teeth and
then went to bed because I definitely
wanted to
watch another episode of Desperate Housewives.  A
day without an episode of Desperate Housewives
is not a day for me.  So, with
my evening routine, I definitely
made the most of the day.  Bye.